http://www.buckeyefabricating.com/page/privacy

NAICS:
This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which BUCKEYE
FABRICATING COMPANY collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each, a “User”) of the www.buckeyefabricating.com website (“Site”). This privacy policy applies to the Site and all products and services offered by BUCKEYE
FABRICATING COMPANY.
Personal Identification Information
We may collect personal identification information from Users in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when Users visit our site, place an order, subscribe to the newsletter, fill out a form, and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available on our Site. Users may be asked for, as appropriate, name, email address, mailing address, phone number, credit card information. Users may, however, visit our Site anonymously. We will collect personal identification information from Users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Users can always refuse to supply personally identification information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain Site related activities.
Non-Personal Identification Information
We may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our Site. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about Users means of connection to our Site, such as the operating system and the Internet service providers utilized and other similar information.
Web Browser Cookies
Our Site may use “cookies” to enhance User experience. User’s web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. User may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of the Site may not function properly.
BUCKEYE
FABRICATING COMPANY may collect and use Users personal information for the following purposes:
To Personalize User Experience
We may use information in the aggregate to understand how our Users as a group use the services and resources provided on our Site.
To Improve Our Site
We may use feedback you provide to improve our products and services.
To Run a Promotion, Contest, Survey or Other Site Feature
To send Users information they agreed to receive about topics we think will be of interest to them.
To Send Periodic Emails
We may use the email address to send User information and updates pertaining to their order. It may also be used to respond to their inquiries, questions, and/or other requests. If User decides to opt-in to our mailing list, they will receive emails that may include company news, updates, related product or service information, etc. If at any time the User would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.
How We Protect Your Information
We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our Site.
Sensitive and private data exchange between the Site and its Users happens over a SSL secured communication channel and is encrypted and protected with digital signatures.
Sharing Your Personal Information
We do not sell, trade, or rent Users personal identification information to others. We may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal identification information regarding visitors and users with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined above.
Third Party Websites
Users may find advertising or other content on our Site that link to the sites and services of our partners, suppliers, advertisers, sponsors, licensors and other third parties. We do not control the content or links that appear on these sites and are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our Site. In addition, these sites or services, including their content and links, may be constantly changing. These sites and services may have their own privacy policies and customer service policies. Browsing and interaction on any other website, including websites which have a link to our Site, is subject to that website’s own terms and policies.
Changes to This Privacy Policy
BUCKEYE
FABRICATING COMPANY has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will revise the updated date at the bottom of this page. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.
Your Acceptance of These Terms
By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy and terms of service. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.
Contacting Us
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please contact us at:
BUCKEYE
FABRICATING COMPANY
245 S. PIONEER BLVD.,
SPRINGBORO, OHIO 45066
PHONE: 1-800-688-9821
Intellectual Property Rights
BUCKEYE
FABRICATING COMPANY (“Company”) retains all right, title and interest in and to the buckeyefabricating.com Web site and all portions thereof, the Content (as defined below), features, products and services provided on or through the Site (collectively “Products”), the web site, content and products hereafter (the “Site”) and all related intellectual property, which includes, without limitation, the business processes, procedures, methods and techniques used with the Site and the Products, and all patent rights, copyright rights, sui generis database rights, trademark rights, trade secret rights and other proprietary rights therein throughout the world (collectively, “Intellectual Property”). The Products may be used, downloaded, displayed, and printed by you solely for your personal, internal and non-commercial use. You may not otherwise use, modify, publish, broadcast, transmit, transfer or sell, rent, lease, reproduce, create derivative works from, distribute, circulate, disseminate, perform, link, display, or in any way exploit any Product or Intellectual Property, in whole or in part, except as expressly permitted in any written agreement you may have with Company or with the prior written consent of Company. You are prohibited from modifying any computer software provided on the Site in any manner or form, or from using modified versions of such software including, without limitation, for the purpose of obtaining unauthorized access to any portion of the Site or any Product.
Brands, company names, product names and logos on the Site are the trademarks, service marks, or trade names of Company, its partners or licensors. The use of any Company (or any Company partner or licensor) trademark, trade name, or service mark without Company’s (or the appropriate owner’s) express written consent is strictly prohibited.
Links
The Site may contain links to other Internet Web sites or resources. Company does not endorse and is not responsible or liable in any way for any content, advertising, services or goods on or available from such Web sites or resources.
Liability Limitation and Disclaimers
THIS SITE AND THE PRODUCTS ARE PROVIDED ON AN “AS-IS” AND “WHERE-IS” BASIS. COMPANY EXPRESSLY DISCLAIMS ALL WARRANTIES OF ANY KIND, WHETHER EXPRESS OR IMPLIED INCLUDING, WITHOUT LIMITATION, THE IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE AND NON-INFRINGEMENT. COMPANY DOES NOT REPRESENT OR WARRANT THAT (I) THE SITE WILL MEET YOUR EXPECTATIONS OR REQUIREMENTS, (II) THE SITE WILL BE UNINTERRUPTED, TIMELY, SECURE, OR ERROR-FREE, (III) ANY RESULTS OR CONTENT THAT MAY BE OBTAINED FROM THE USE OF THE SITE WILL BE ACCURATE, TIMELY, COMPLETE OR RELIABLE, AND (IV) ANY ERRORS WILL BE CORRECTED.
COMPANY IS NOT RESPONSIBLE AND WILL HAVE NO LIABILITY FOR (I) HARDWARE, SOFTWARE, OTHER ITEMS OR ANY SERVICES PROVIDED BY ANY PERSONS OR ENTITIES OTHER THAN COMPANY OR (II) THE FAILURES OF THE INTERNET OR ANY DATA OR TELECOMMUNICATIONS EQUIPMENT, SYSTEM OR NETWORK USED IN CONNECTION WITH THE SITE OR THE PRODUCTS.
TO THE MAXIMUM EXTENT PERMITTED BY LAW, COMPANY WILL NOT BE LIABLE UNDER ANY CONTRACT, NEGLIGENCE, STRICT LIABILITY OR OTHER LEGAL OR EQUITABLE THEORY FOR (I) ANY SPECIAL, INCIDENTAL, INDIRECT, CONSEQUENTIAL OR EXEMPLARY DAMAGES ARISING OUT OF OR IN CONNECTION WITH THE SITE OR PRODUCTS, EVEN IF COMPANY HAS BEEN ADVISED OF SUCH DAMAGES OR THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES; (II) THE COST OF PROCURING SUBSTITUTE GOODS, SERVICES, OR TECHNOLOGY; (III) PERSONAL INJURY, INCLUDING, WITHOUT LIMITATION, DEATH, CAUSED BY YOUR USE OR MISUSE OF THE SITE OR THE PRODUCTS; OR (IV) AGGREGATE LIABILITY IN EXCESS OF $10.
SOME JURISDICTIONS DO NOT ALLOW THE EXCLUSION OF CERTAIN WARRANTIES OR THE LIMITATION OR EXCLUSION OF LIABILITY FOR INCIDENTAL OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES. ACCORDINGLY, SOME OF THE ABOVE LIMITATIONS MAY NOT APPLY TO YOU. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO THE FOREGOING TERMS AND CONDITIONS, YOU ARE NOT PERMITTED TO USE OR VIEW THE SITE.
Contact Us
Call 1-800-688-9821 or fill & send below!
DOWNLOAD NOW
Your Tank Is Ready For Delivery
Submit your request for proposal now. The sooner we get started on your custom steel tank, the sooner it’s rolling out our door to your facility.
Address: 245 S. Pioneer Blvd.,
Springboro, Ohio 45066
Tel: 937.746.9822 | Fax 937.746.9823
PRESS RELEASE
COPYRIGHT © 2020. BUCKEYE FABRICATING COMPANY. ALL RIGHTS RESERVED
